<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Motivation</title>
    <link>https://@@@GITHUB@@@code-motivation/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Code Motivation</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 20:11:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://@@@GITHUB@@@code-motivation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>      
      <description>Simplicity is prerequisite for reliability. – Edsger W. Dijkstra</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>A program that produces incorrect results twice as fast is infinitely slower. – John Osterhout</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>The most effective debugging tool is still careful thought, coupled with judiciously placed print statements. – Brian W. Kernighan, in the paper Unix for Beginners (1979)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>One of my most productive days was throwing away 1000 lines of code. – Ken Thompson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>The cheapest, fastest, and most reliable components are those that aren’t there. – Gordon Bell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Any code of your own that you haven’t looked at for six or more months might as well have been written by someone else. – Eagleson’s Law</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Good code is its own best documentation. – Steve McConnell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Optimism is an occupational hazard of programming; feedback is the treatment. – Kent Beck</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>First, solve the problem. Then, write the code. – John Johnson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Computers are useless. They can only give you answers. – Pablo Picasso</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>One of the best programming skills you can have is knowing when to walk away for awhile. – Oscar Godson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>No one in the brief history of computing has ever written a piece of perfect software. It’s unlikely that you’ll be the first. – Andy Hunt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Rules of Optimization:
      Rule 1: Don’t do it.
      Rule 2 (for experts only): Don’t do it yet. – Michael A. Jackson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Every great developer you know got there by solving problems they were unqualified to solve until they actually did it. – Patrick McKenzie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>What one programmer can do in one month, two programmers can do in two months. – Fredrick Brooks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Most good programmers do programming not because they expect to get paid or get adulation by the public, but because it is fun to program. – Linus Torvalds</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>Sometimes it pays to stay in bed on Monday, rather than spending the rest of the week debugging Monday’s code. – Christopher Thompson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>      
      <description>In theory, theory and practice are the same. In practice, they’re not. – Yoggi Berra</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>